OWEN MOOGK

512 Little Dover Cres, Waterloo 🏠 226-989-0602 % owenmoogk@gmail.com 🖂

Have had plenty of experience in customer

Am proficient in Microsoft Office software, GSuite, and other basic computer programs.

CSS, JavaScript, React, and Django.

OnShape and Solidworks.

pick up new skills in any domain.

Intermediate level industrial design using

service, carrying a positive attitude, teamwork,

Have been in many leadership positions, learning and implementing problem solving and time

Experienced in website development, using HTML,

Novice graphical design and video editing skills.

Am a quick learner, and am willing and able to

Responsible technology enthusiast, with experience in customer service.

EDUCATION



SKILLS

and cooperation.

management skills.



HIGH SCHOOL

September 2018 - Present



Have completed all of my 24 classes with honor roll awards in all, and currently have a 95% grade average through high school. I have also been selected for advanced placement in mathematics, microeconomics, physics, and chemistry.

EXPERIENCE



MERRY HILL GOLF

May 2020 - Present

CLUBHOUSE EMPLOYEE

Demonstrated excellent customer service by using skills such as communication, responsibility and cooperation. Navigated difficult situations by acknowledging customer concerns and being accountable.

WMBA

May 2017 - May 2020

UMPIRE

Was a paid umpire for the WMBA for 3 years, navigating difficult situations, and employing management and cooperation skills, whilst promoting kindness, sportsmanship and fun.

FIRST ROBOTICS

August 2018 - Present

SUB-TEAM LEAD

Led a subteam of robotics students using project management and teamwork skills to build a mechanism to complete a given task, whilst learning leadership skills transferrable to any workplace.

DUKE OF EDINBURGH AWARD

ACHIEVEMENTS

Awarded Bronze and Silver Duke of Edinburgh's award for exceptional community service and personal growth.

SHAD

I was accepted into a competitive month-long business and science program held at universities across the country.

COMMUNITY ACTIVITIES



International Business Competition

I advanced to the provincial competition in Toronto by demonstrating quick thinking and business skills, and achieveing withing the top 10% of competitiors.

CHOOSE TO LEAD

Leadership Program

I was accepted into the 4 year prestegious Choose to Lead program by demonstrating teamwork, cooperation, management, and leadership skills. It is structured around leadership in the community and building interpersonal skills.

